http://www.syncrosvnclient.com/terms_of_use.html

Syncro SVN Client      AboutHomeFeatures Subversion 1.8Repository BrowserAdvanced Working CopyResource HistoryDirectory Change SetRevision GraphSubversion PropertiesCheck DifferencesDetailed Author InfoBuilt-in Text EditorsResolving ConflictsBug Tracking IntegrationFlexible User InterfaceScreenshotsDownloadsDownloadDocumentationSoftware ArchiveTry nowFree Trial licenseShopBuy nowCustomersFAQRegistration codeSupportVideo TutorialsSupportForumSyncro SVN Logos
Video TutorialsSupportForumSyncro SVN LogosOur website uses cookies. Find out more about cookies.I understand. Hide this message.
Terms of Use
Welcome to the Web site (the "Site") of Syncro Soft (referred to as "Syncro," "we,"
"us," or "our" herein). Via the Site, Syncro makes a number of resources available to you,
including information, software, products, downloads, documents, communications, files,
text, graphics, publications, content, tools, and services such as technical support.
PLEASE READ THE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THE SITE. By accessing and using the
Site in any way, including browsing the Site, using any information, content, or services,
downloading any software or files, and placing orders for products, you agree to abide by
the terms of use described on this page.
IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THE TERMS OF USE,
PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE IN ANY WAY. The Terms of Use are a binding agreement between
Syncro and you. If you use the Site on behalf of an employer, you represent that you are
authorized to accept these Terms of Use on behalf of your employer.
Syncro is continually improving and adding new functionality and features to this Site.
These improvements (or changes in the law) may require changes to these Terms of Use.
Accordingly, we reserve the right to update or modify these Terms of Use at any time without
prior notice. We will do so by posting an updated or modified version of these Terms of Use
on this Site. Your use of this Site following any such change constitutes your agreement to
comply with and be bound by these Terms of Use. For this reason, we encourage you to review
these Terms of Use regularly. You may review these Terms of Use at any time by clicking on
the button marked "Terms of Use" at the bottom of each page of this Site.
Ownership of Copyrights in Content
All of the text, data, images, graphics, audio, video and audio-video clips, software
applications, and all of the other information, materials and tools made available to you
through this Site (collectively, the "Content") is copyrighted under United States law and
applicable international copyright laws and treaty provisions. Unauthorized use of the
Site’s content may violate such laws and these Terms of Use. The copyrights in the Content
are owned by Syncro or third parties who have licensed their materials to Syncro, all
rights reserved.
The entire Content of this Site is copyrighted as a collective work under United
States copyright law and applicable international copyright laws and treaties, and Syncro
owns the copyright in the selection, coordination, arrangement and enhancement of the
Content. Any rights not expressly granted by these Terms of Use or any applicable end user
license agreements are reserved by Syncro and/or its vendors and licensors.
Software Use Restrictions
Any software that is made available to download from the Website (the "Software") is the
copyrighted work of Syncro and/or Third Party Providers. Use of the Software is governed by
the terms of the end user license agreement, if any, which accompanies or is included with
the Software (the "License Agreement"). An end user will be unable to install any Software
that is accompanied by or includes a License Agreement, unless the end user first agrees to
the terms of the License Agreement. Except as set forth in the applicable License Agreement,
any further copying, reproduction or redistribution of the Software is expressly
prohibited.
Limited product support and maintenance, if any, of the Software is available from
Syncro and/or the Third Party Providers, as the case may be.
SOFTWARE IS WARRANTED, IF AT ALL, IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS OF THE LICENSE AGREEMENT.
EXCEPT AS SET FORTH IN THE LICENSE AGREEMENT, ALL EXPRESS OR IMPLIED CONDITIONS,
REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, INCLUDING ANY IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS
FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT, ARE DISCLAIMED, EXCEPT TO THE EXTENT THAT
SUCH DISCLAIMERS ARE HELD TO BE LEGALLY INVALID.
Terms of Sale
All sales of Software and services by Syncro that are made through the Site are
governed by Syncro's Terms and Conditions
of Sale, and by ordering Software or services from Syncro through the Site, you
agree to be bound by and accept such Terms and Conditions of Sale. The Terms and
Conditions of Sale are subject to change without prior notice at any time, in Syncro's
sole discretion, so you should review the Terms and Conditions of Sale each time you make
a purchase.
Registration
In some instances, you may be required to register to gain access to certain Site
areas or services. If you choose to register on our Site, you agree to (a) provide
accurate, current, and complete information about yourself as prompted by the applicable
registration form, and (b) maintain and update your information (including your email
address) to keep it accurate, current, and complete. You acknowledge that if any
information provided by you is untrue, inaccurate, not current, or incomplete, we reserve
the right to terminate your use of the Site.
Privacy Policy
Please review the Privacy Policy posted on
this Site (the "Privacy Policy") to learn what personal information is collected through
this Site, how it is used and with whom it is shared.
The Privacy Policy is part of these Terms of Use. When you agree to be bound by these
Terms of Use, you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal
information in accordance with our Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to our use of
your personal information as set forth in our Privacy Policy, you may not access or use
this Site.
Trademark Notice
All of the trademarks, service marks and logos displayed on this Site ("the
Trademark(s)") are registered and unregistered trademarks of Syncro, one of its
affiliates, or a third party.
No right, title or interest in any Trademark is transferred to or acquired by you or
your company under these Terms of Use or by virtue of your use of this Site. Except as
expressly permitted under these Terms of Use, you may not reproduce, display or otherwise
use any Trademark without first obtaining written permission from the owner of the
Trademark.
Government Restricted Rights
The Software which may be downloaded, acquired or accessed from this Site is a
"commercial item," as that term is defined at 48 C.F.R. 2.101 (OCT 1995), consisting of
"commercial computer software" and "commercial computer software documentation," as such
terms are used in 48 C.F.R. 12.212 (SEPT 1995). Consistent with 48 C.F.R. 12.212 and 48
C.F.R. 227.7201-1 through 227.7201-4 (JUNE 1995), the Software is provided to U.S.
Government end users with only those rights as are granted to all other end users pursuant
to the terms and conditions set forth in Syncro's standard end user license agreement
accompanying the Software. Further, to the extent that any "technical data," as that term
is used in 48 C.F.R. 12.211, is provided in connection with any Content or software
downloaded, acquired or accessed through the Site, the government shall acquire only the
technical data and the rights in that data customarily provided to the public with a
commercial item or process.
Third-Party Information
Some of the information, articles and other materials available through this Site are
provided to us by third parties. These third party materials are provided for your and
your company's interest and convenience only. Although we select with care the vendors who
provide these materials to us, we do not endorse these materials or the vendors who supply
them to us, nor do we warrant or represent that these materials are current, accurate,
complete or reliable. It is your responsibility to evaluate the currency, accuracy,
completeness and reliability of all third-party information obtained or provided through
this Site. You use these materials at your own risk and subject to any third-party
disclaimers.
Links to Other Sites
This Site contains links to websites that are not operated by Syncro. These links are
provided for your and your company's reference and convenience only, and do not imply that
Syncro or its affiliates endorse the material on these websites. Syncro does not control
these sites and is not responsible for their content. You access and use these sites
solely at your own risk. These Terms of Use, including the Privacy Policy, which is part
of these Terms of Use, do not apply to any other website. If you access another website
through a link on this Site, please take a few minutes to review the terms of use and
privacy statement posted on that website.
Disclaimer of Warranties and Limitation of Liability
THIS WEB SITE IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS," "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF
ANY KIND. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT POSSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, SYNCRO DISCLAIMS ALL
WARRANTIES, EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.
WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, SYNCRO DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THIS WEB SITE
WILL BE AVAILABLE AT ANY PARTICULAR TIME OR LOCATION OR THAT ITS OPERATION WILL BE
UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE. SYNCRO DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING
THE USE, VALIDITY, ACCURACY, CURRENCY OR RELIABILITY OF, OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF, OR
OTHERWISE RESPECTING THIS WEB SITE OR ANY INFORMATION PUBLISHED ON THIS WEB SITE. BECAUSE
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT PERMIT THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES, THESE EXCLUSIONS MAY
NOT APPLY TO YOU.
YOUR USE OF THIS WEB SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES, SHALL SYNCRO,
ITS OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, DIRECTORS, AGENTS, SUPPLIERS, OR OTHER THIRD PARTIES MENTIONED ON
THIS SITE, BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT OR INDIRECT LOSSES OR DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR IN
CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEB SITE OR YOUR RELIANCE ON ANY
INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THIS WEB SITE. THIS IS A COMPREHENSIVE LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
THAT APPLIES TO ALL LOSSES AND DAMAGES OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER, WHETHER DIRECT OR INDIRECT,
GENERAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING WITHOUT
LIMITATION, LOSS OF DATA, REVENUE OR PROFITS. THIS LIMITATION OF LIABILITY APPLIES WHETHER
THE ALLEGED LIABILITY IS BASED ON CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR ANY
OTHER BASIS AND WHETHER OR NOT SYNCRO HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
CERTAIN JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SET FORTH ABOVE, SO THIS
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IF ANY PART OF THIS LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
IS FOUND TO BE INVALID OR UNENFORCEABLE FOR ANY REASON, THEN THE AGGREGATE LIABILITY OF
SYNCRO UNDER SUCH CIRCUMSTANCES FOR LIABILITIES THAT OTHERWISE WOULD HAVE BEEN LIMITED
SHALL NOT EXCEED FIVE HUNDRED ($500.00) DOLLARS.
Waiver
Our failure at any time to require performance of any provision of these Terms of Use
or to exercise any right provided for herein shall not be deemed a waiver of such
provision or such right. All waivers must be in writing and signed by the party to be
bound. Unless the written waiver contains an express statement to the contrary, no waiver
by Syncro of any breach of any provision of these Terms of Use of any right provided for
herein shall be construed as a waiver of any continuing or succeeding breach of such
provision, a waiver of the provision itself, or a waiver of any right under these Terms of
Use.
Severability
If any provision of these Terms of Use is held by a court of competent jurisdiction to
be contrary to law, such provision shall be changed and interpreted so as to best
accomplish the objectives of the original provision to the fullest extent allowed by law
and the remaining provisions of these Terms of Use shall remain in full force and effect.
Governing Law and Jurisdiction
This Site is administered by Syncro Soft from its home offices in Craiova, Remus 5A,
Romania. Unless otherwise specified, the Content is presented solely for the purpose of
promoting Syncro and its products.
You agree to comply with all laws, rules and regulations applicable to your
downloading or use of the Software and Content available on or through this Site,
including, but not limited to, all United States export control laws, rules and
regulations. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, no Software or Content may
be downloaded or exported into countries embargoed by the U.S. Treasury Office of Foreign
Asset Control (OFAC); or anyone on the United States Treasury Department's list of
Specially Designated Nationals or the U.S. Commerce Department's Table of Deny Orders.
Syncro does not authorize the transfer, by any means, of any Software, Content or
technical data from this Site to any jurisdiction prohibited by the United States export
laws. You may not use, export or re-export the Software or Content, or any copy or
adaptation thereof, in violation of any applicable laws or regulations, including without
limitation United States export laws and regulations.
These Terms of Use will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of
Romania, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of laws. You and Syncro each
agree to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located in
Romania. The United Nations Convention on International Sale of Goods shall not apply to
these Terms of Use.
Entire Agreement
This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and Syncro with respect to
your access to and/or use of this Site (but not the Software downloaded from this Site).
This Agreement shall not be amended except as expressly set forth herein.
Questions or comments regarding this Website or these Terms of Use should be directed
to
or by phone at
+40-251-461480.
News
April 8, 2015: Syncro Subversion(SVN) Client
10.1 is available.
June 10, 2014: Syncro Subversion(SVN) Client
10 is available.
Video Demonstration
see more
Quotes
We could not be without Syncro SVN Client to manage our code
repository. It's easy to use, powerful and intuitive.
© 2002-2018 SyncRO Soft SRL. All rights reserved. | Sitemap | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
|
This website was created &
generated with <oXygen/>® XML Editor
